http://www.tradingday.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
The following privacy policy provides you with information on the nature, extent, purpose and duration of the processing of personal data and your rights as a data subject.
Processing takes place within the framework of the applicable data protection regulations.
1. Responsible parties (controller):
Andre Vieth Fewo Marketing GmbH
c/o Mindspace
Friedrichstrasse 68
10117 Berlin
Managing Director:
Andre Vieth
Telephone:
0172 6022473
E-Mail Address:
andre@ostsee-reisen.de
Register court:
Amtsgericht Charlottenburg
Registration number:
HRB 195538
In the following, the controller will also be called operator.
2. Types of processed data
2.1. Device data and usage data
When accessing the website of the operator, the following data is automatically transmitted to our server by your browser:
Date and time of access
URL of the referring website
Requested website
Size of the data sent
Browser type and browser version
Operating system
Your IP address at the time of access
Cookies
For a server to be able to deliver data to a recipient, it needs the IP address of the recipient. An IP address is a unique address on a network and is assigned to devices attached to the network. It makes the devices of the receiver addressable and therefore accessible.
The operator uses cookies.
Cookies are textual information that can be stored and read on your computer.
Cookies may be set by the operator himself or, if third-party services are involved, also by these third-party services.
As part of a cookie, not only data but also unique identifiers of a user can be stored (cookie IDs). In this way, cookies and thus also the storing devices can be clearly identified.
You can prevent the setting of cookies by configuring your Internet browser accordingly. If the blocking of cookies results in restrictions of certain features, it will be outlined under the respective processing purposes below. In addition, you can delete previously set cookies in your Internet browser or as part of separate software solutions.
3. Purposes of processing
3.1. Statistics and analysis of user behavior (internal processing)
The device and usage data (2.1) is processed for statistical purposes and the analysis of user behavior according to the following principles:
As part of the processing, the IP address is shortened and thus anonymized. Identification of the user via the IP address is therefore no longer possible.
The shortened IP addresses are needed to provide statistics on the geographic origin of Web page accesses.
The data is processed separately from personal data that is collected elsewhere (eg data from contact forms or data that become known after login with username and password).
As part of the processing, a cookie with a unique identifier is set. The identifier differs from identifiers that can be associated with personal data (eg the id assigned to you when logging in with username and password).
Legal basis of processing
There is a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR.
In particular, the collection of data for statistical purposes and for user behavior analysis is needed to improve the quality of the service.
Balance of interests
The anonymization of IP addresses and the separate processing of personal data that is collected elsewhere make it impossible to assign personal data to specific users.
Opt-Out
You can suppress the storage of cookies or delete cookies later (see 2.1.).
3.2. Statistics and analysis of user behavior by Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google LLC.
Google Analytics generates statistics and user behavior reports for the operator of this site.
For example, Google analyses which pages or page types have been requested by a user or groups of users, the order in which the pages have been requested, what hardware and software was used and how long users have visited a page or how often specific pages or page types were requested.
Google Analytics uses cookies, text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of your use of the website. With the cookie, device and usage data is stored (see 2.1.).
For privacy reasons, the service is used as follows:
The so-called user ID function is deactivated. Thus, it is NOT possible to assign data, sessions and interactions across multiple devices to a pseudonymous user ID and it is also NOT possible to analyze a user’s activities across devices.
The function IP masking (“anonymizeIP”) is activated. It will not process your full IP address, but an anonymous or abridged version of the IP address. Identification of the user via the IP address is therefore no longer possible. The anonymization of the IP address occurs within member states of the European Union or other contracting states of the Agreement on the European Economic Area.
When collecting the data, no further personal data will be transmitted to Google Analytics (eg personal data collected directly on the operator side).
Google will never associate your IP address with other Google data.
More information about Google Analytics can be found at
https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/en.html
The Google Privacy Policy can be found at
https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Purpose of processing
The purpose of processing is to analyze user behavior for individual anonymised users or as part of aggregated user data, as well as to measure success in the form of statistics on the number of users and the intensity of use over time.
Legal basis of processing
There is a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR.
In particular, the collection of statistical data is vital for the operation and improvement of the service.
Reasons for balance of interests
The anonymization of IP addresses and the lack of transmission of unique user IDs makes it impossible to assign data to specific users.
Recipients or categories of recipients
Google LLC
1600 Amphitheater Parkway
Mountain View, CA 94043
USA
Transmission to non-EU-foreign countries
The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there.
A commissioned-processing contract has been closed with Google.
Storage duration or its criteria
Deletion is not necessary due to the lack of unique user IDs.
Opt-Out
The browser add-on for disabling Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, dc.js) allows website visitors to prevent Google Analytics from using your data. The browser add-on can be downloaded from the following address.
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de
You can set a deactivation cookie: Please click on the following link to deactivate Google Analytics Deactivate Google Analytics
The deactivation of the tracking has no effect on the functionality of the website.
Automated decision-making and profiling
Automated decision-making or profiling is not employed.
3.3. Google AdSense
This website uses Google AdSense to deliver ads to its users. Google AdSense is a service of Google LLC.
If the user agrees, Google AdSense uses cookies to deliver targeted advertising based on past visitor behavior.
The information received via the cookies, your IP address and data about the delivered advertising are sent to a Google server in the USA.
Google may transfer this information to third parties if required by law or if Google commissions data processing to third parties.
For privacy reasons the service will be used as follows:
The service is ony active after prior consent by the user.
Google only presents non-personalized ads to users in the EEA.
Non-personalized ads use contextual information rather than a user’s previous behavior.
These ads do not use cookies for personalized ads, but cookies that are required for frequency capping, aggregated ad reporting, and to prevent fraud and abuse.
Legal basis of processing
- Prior consent by the user is required for the service to be enabled (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR). The user can enable or disable the service via a menu displayed automatically during the first visit.
- There is a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR, since the offer is free of charge for the end user and the cost will be covered through advertising revenues.
Recipients or categories of recipients
Google LLC
1600 Amphitheater Parkway
Mountain View, CA 94043
United States
Opt-Out
You can prevent the use of cookies as follows:
by a corresponding setting in the menu under the link “Cookie Consent” at www.tradingday.com, the menu is also presented to the user on the first visit of the site
by a corresponding setting in your browser
by
opting out of interest-based ads on Google
by
opting out of interest-based ads from vendors that are part of the About Ads self-regulatory campaign
by using browser plug-ins to block ads
4. Disclosure of data to third parties
4.1. Web hosting
The data of the operator is processed on servers of external web hosting service providers.
Commissioned-processing contracts have been closed with the service providers in accordance with Art. 28 GDPR. The data is processed in the territory of the US.
5. Rights of the persons concerned
You have the following rights under the General Data Protection Regulation:
Right of access by the data subject in accordance with Art. 15 GDPR
You have the right to request confirmation from us as to whether personal data relating to you is being processed and to information on the nature, extent, purpose and duration of the processing and the disclosure of the data to third parties.
Right to rectification according to Art. 16 GDPR
You have the right to demand immediate correction of incorrect personal data concerning you.
Right to erasure according to Art. 17 GDPR
You have the right to demand that personal data relating to you be deleted without delay, inter alia, if the processing is no longer necessary for the intended purpose or if you revoke a previously granted consent and if so there is no other legal basis for storage.
Right to restriction of processing according to Art. 18 GDPR
You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing, especially if a deletion is not possible for legal reasons.
Right to data portability According to Art. 20 GDPR
You have the right to receive the personal data that you have provided to us in a structured, common and machine-readable format and to transmit the data to third parties.
Right to object according to Art. 21 GDPR
You have the right to object to the processing of personal data relating to you on the basis of your particular situation at any time, in accordance with Article 6 (1) (e) or (f); this also applies to profiling based on these provisions.
Automated individual decision-making, including profiling according to Art. 22 GDPR
You have the right not to be subjected to a decision based solely on automated processing, which will have a legal effect on you or significantly affects you in a similar manner.
Withdrawal of consent according to Art. 7 Abs. 3 GDPR
If the processing of your data is based on a consent, you have the right to revoke your consent at any time.
Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority according to Art. 77 GDPR
Without prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, every data subject shall have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of his or her habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement if the data subject considers that the processing of personal data relating to him or her infringes this Regulation.
Datenschutzerklärung
In der folgenden Datenschutzerklärung erhalten Sie Informationen zu Art, Umfang, Zweck und Dauer der Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten und zu Ihren Rechten als Betroffener. Die Verarbeitung erfolgt im Rahmen der datenschutzrechtlichen Bestimmungen.
1. Verantwortlicher
Andre Vieth Fewo Marketing GmbH
c/o Mindspace
Friedrichstraße 68
10117 Berlin
Geschäftsführer:
Andre Vieth
Telefon:
0172 6022473
E-Mail-Adresse:
andre@ostsee-reisen.de
Registergericht:
Amtsgericht Charlottenburg
Registernummer:
HRB 195538
Der Verantwortliche wird im Folgenden auch Betreiber genannt.
2. Arten der verarbeiteten Daten
2.1. Endgerätedaten und Nutzungsdaten
Beim Zugriff auf die Webseite des Betreibers werden durch Ihren Browser automatisch u.a. folgende Daten an unseren Server übermittelt:
Datum und Uhrzeit des Zugriffs
URL der verweisenden Internetseite
aufgerufene Internetseite
Größe der gesendeten Daten
Browsertyp und Browserversion
Betriebssystem
Ihre IP-Adresse zum Zeitpunkt des Zugriffs
Cookies
Damit ein Server Daten an einen Empfänger ausliefern kann, benötigt er die IP-Adresse des Empfängers. Eine IP-Adresse ist eine eindeutige Adresse in einem Netzwerk und wird Geräten zugewiesen, die an das Netz angebunden sind. Sie macht die Geräte des Empfängers adressierbar und damit erreichbar.
Im Rahmen des Internetangebotes des Betreibers werden Cookies gesetzt.
Cookies sind Textinformationen, die auf Ihrem Computer gespeichert und ausgelesen werden können.
Die Setzung der Cookies kann durch den Betreiber selbst, bei Einbindung von Drittdiensten auch durch diese Drittdienste erfolgen.
Im Rahmen eines Cookies können neben Daten auch eindeutige Kennungen eines Benutzers gespeichert werden (Cookie-IDs). Auf diese Weise können Cookies und damit auch die speichernden Endgeräte eindeutig identifiziert werden.
Sie können das Setzen der Cookies durch eine entsprechende Einstellung Ihres Internetbrowsers für die Zukunft verhindern. Sofern es dadurch zu Einschränkungen der Nutzung kommt, wird dies unter den jeweiligen Verarbeitungszwecken weiter unten aufgeführt. Sie können zudem bereits gesetzte Cookies in Ihrem Internetbrowser oder im Rahmen separater Softwarelösungen regelmäßig löschen oder löschen lassen.
3. Zwecke der Verarbeitung
3.1. Erfolgsmessung und Auswertung des Nutzerverhaltens (interne Verarbeitung)
Die unter 2.1. erfassten Endgerätedaten werden für die Erfolgsmessung und die Auswertung des Nutzerverhaltens nach folgenden Grundsätzen verarbeitet:
Im Rahmen der Verarbeitung wird die IP-Adresse gekürzt und somit anonymisiert. Eine Identifizierung des Nutzers über die IP-Adresse ist somit nicht mehr möglich.
Die gekürzten IP-Adressen werden benötigt, um Statistiken zur geographischen Herkunft von Webseitenzugriffen zu erstellen.
Die Daten werden getrennt von personenbezogenen Daten verarbeitet, die an anderer Stelle erhoben werden (z.B. Daten aus Kontaktformularen oder Daten, die nach Anmeldung mit Nutzernamen und Passwort bekannt werden).
Im Rahmen der Verarbeitung wird ein Cookie mit einer eindeutigen Kennung gesetzt. Die Kennung unterscheidet sich von Kennungen, die mit personenbezogenen Daten in Verbindung gebracht werden können (z.B. eigene Kennung bei Anmeldung mit Nutzernamen und Passwort).
Rechtsgrundlage der Verarbeitung
Es liegt ein berechtigtes Interesse im Sinne des Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit. f DSGVO vor.
Insbesondere sind die Erhebung von Statistiken zur Erfolgsmessung und die Analyse des Nutzerverhaltens zur Verbesserung der Qualität des Dienstes notwendig.
Gründe der Interessenabwägung
Durch die Anonymisierung der IP-Adressen und der separaten Verarbeitung von personenbezogenen Daten, die anderweitig erfasst werden, ist eine Zuordnung von Daten zu konkreten Nutzern nicht möglich.
Opt-Out
Sie können die Speicherung von Cookies unterdrücken oder Cookies nachträglich löschen (siehe 2.1.).
3.2. Erfolgsmessung und Auswertung des Nutzerverhaltens durch Google Analytics
Diese Website benutzt Google Analytics, einen Webanalysedienst der Google LLC.
Google Analytics erstellt für den Betreiber dieser Seite Statistiken und Auswertungen zum Nutzerverhalten.
Ausgewertet werden zum Beispiel, welche Seiten oder Seitentypen des Betreibers ein Benutzer oder Nutzergruppen aufgerufen haben, in welcher Abfolge dieser Abruf erfolgt ist, über welche Hardware und Software der Abruf erfolgt ist, wie lange Nutzer eine Seite besucht haben oder wie oft bestimmte Seiten oder Seitentypen aufgerufen wurden.
Google Analytics verwendet Cookies, Textdateien, die auf Ihrem Computer gespeichert werden und die eine Analyse der Benutzung der Website durch Sie ermöglichen. Mit dem Cookie werden die unter 2.1. aufgeführten Endgerätedaten und Nutzungsdaten gespeichert.
Aus Gründen des Datenschutzes wird der Dienst wie folgt verwendet:
Die sogenannte User-ID Funktion ist deaktiviert. Somit ist es NICHT möglich, Daten, Sitzungen und Interaktionen über mehrere Geräte hinweg einer pseudonymen User-ID zuzuordnen und es ist auch NICHT möglich, die Aktivitäten eines Nutzers geräteübergreifend zu analysieren.
Die Funktion IP-Maskierung (“anonymizeIP”) ist aktiviert. Es wird also nicht Ihre vollständige IP-Adresse verarbeitet, sondern eine anonymisierte bzw. gekürzte Version der IP-Adresse. Eine Identifizierung des Nutzers über die IP-Adresse ist somit nicht mehr möglich. Die Kürzung der IP-Adresse erfolgt innerhalb von Mitgliedstaaten der Europäischen Union oder in anderen Vertragsstaaten des Abkommens über den Europäischen Wirtschaftsraum.
Es werden bei der Erfassung der Daten keine weiteren personenbezogenen Daten an Google Analytics übermittelt (z.B. personenbezogene Daten, die direkt auf der Betreiberseite gesammelt wurden).
Google wird in keinem Fall Ihre IP-Adresse mit anderen Daten von Google in Verbindung bringen.
Weitere Informationen zu Google Analytics finden Sie unter
https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html
Die Google Datenschutzerklärung finden Sie unter
https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de
Zweck der Verarbeitung
Zweck der Verarbeitung ist die Analyse des Nutzerverhaltens für einzelne anonymisierte Nutzer oder im Rahmen von aggregierten Nutzerdaten sowie die Erfolgsmessung im Rahmen von Statistiken zur Anzahl der Nutzer und der Intensität der Nutzung im zeitlichen Verlauf.
Rechtsgrundlage der Verarbeitung
Es liegt ein berechtigtes Interesse im Sinne des Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit. f DSGVO vor.
Insbesondere ist die Erhebung von Erfolgskennziffern für den Betrieb des Dienstes zwingend notwendig.
Gründe der Interessenabwägung
Durch die Anonymisierung der IP-Adressen und der fehlenden Übermittlung von eindeutigen Nutzerkennungen ist eine Zuordnung von Daten zu konkreten Nutzern nicht möglich.
Empfänger oder Kategorien von Empfängern
Google LLC
1600 Amphitheatre Parkway
Mountain View, CA 94043
USA
Übermittlung ins Nicht-EU- Ausland (Drittland)
Die durch den Cookie erzeugten Informationen über Ihre Benutzung dieser Website werden an einen Server von Google in den USA übertragen und dort gespeichert.
Es wurde ein Auftragsverarbeitungsvertrag mit Google abgeschlossen.
Speicherdauer oder deren Kriterien
Eine Löschung ist aufgrund des Fehlens von eindeutigen Nutzerkennungen nicht notwendig.
Opt-Out
Mithilfe des Browser-Add-ons zur Deaktivierung von Google Analytics-JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, dc.js) können Webseiten-Besucher verhindern, dass Google Analytics Ihre Daten verwendet. Das Browser Add-on kann unter folgender Adresse heruntergeladen werden und muss anschließend installiert werden.
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de
Setzen eines Deaktivierungscookies: Bitte klicken Sie hierzu auf den folgenden Link
Google Analytics deaktivieren
Die Abschaltung des Trackings hat keine Auswirkungen auf die Nutzungsmöglichkeiten der Webseite.
automatisierte Entscheidungsfindung und Profiling
Eine automatisierte Entscheidungsfindung oder ein Profiling finden nicht statt.
3.3. Google AdSense
Diese Website verwendet Google AdSense zur Einbindung von Werbeanzeigen. Google AdSense ist ein Dienst der Google LLC.
Sofern der Nutzer zustimmt, verwendet Google AdSense Cookies, um basierend auf dem vorangegangenen Besucherverhalten der Nutzer zielgerichtete Werbung ausliefern zu können.
Die über die Cookies erhaltenen Informationen, Ihre IP-Adresse sowie Daten über die ausgelieferte Werbung werden an einen Server von Google in den USA geschickt und verarbeitet.
Google wird diese gesammelten Informationen möglicherweise an Dritte weitergeben, wenn dies gesetzlich erforderlich ist oder Google gegenüber Dritten die Datenverarbeitung in Auftrag gibt.
Aus Gründen des Datenschutzes wird der Dienst wie folgt verwendet:
Die Nutzung von Google AdSense erfolgt nach vorheriger Einwilligung durch den Nutzer.
Google präsentiert Nutzern im EWR ausschließlich nicht personalisierte Anzeigen.
Bei nicht personalisierten Anzeigen werden Kontextinformationen herangezogen und nicht das bisherige Verhalten eines Nutzers.
Für solche Anzeigen werden zwar keine Cookies für personalisierte Anzeigen eingesetzt, aber Cookies, die für das Frequency Capping, für zusammengefasste Anzeigenberichte und zum Bekämpfen von Betrug und Missbrauch notwendig sind.
Rechtsgrundlage der Verarbeitung
- Der Nutzer muss beim Aufruf der Seite der Setzung von Cookies im Sinne des Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit. a im Rahmen von Google AdSense zustimmen.
- Es liegt ein berechtigtes Interesse im Sinne des Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit. f DSGVO vor, da das Angebot für den Endnutzer kostenlos ist und die Finanzierung über Werbung erfolgt.
Empfänger oder Kategorien von Empfängern
Google LLC
1600 Amphitheatre Parkway
Mountain View, CA 94043
USA
Opt-Out
Sie können den Einsatz von Cookies folgendermaßen verhindern:
durch eine entsprechende Einstellung im Menü unter dem Link “Cookie Consent” unter www.tradingday.com und beim erstmaligen Aufruf der Seite, bei dem das Menü automatisch erscheint
durch eine entsprechende Einstellung in Ihrem Browser
durch Deaktivierung der interessenbezogenen Anzeigen bei Google
durch Deaktivierung der interessenbezogenen Anzeigen der Anbieter, die Teil der Selbstregulierungskampagne „About Ads“ sind
durch Nutzung von Browser-Plugins zur Blockierung von Werbeanzeigen
4. Weitergabe der Daten an Dritte
4.1. Webhosting
Die Daten des Betreibers werden auf Servern von externen Webhosting-Dienstleistern verarbeitet. Mit den Dienstleistern wurden Auftragsverarbeitungsverträge gemäß Art. 28 DSGVO geschlossen. Die Verarbeitung der Daten erfolgt in den USA.
5. Rechte der betroffenen Personen
Sie haben im Rahmen der Datenschutz-Grundverordnung folgende Rechte:
Recht auf Auskunft gemäß Art. 15 DSGVO
Sie haben das Recht, von uns eine Bestätigung darüber zu verlangen, ob Sie betreffende personenbezogene Daten verarbeitet werden sowie Information zu Art, Umfang, Zweck und Dauer der Verarbeitung und zur Weitergabe der Daten an Dritte zu erhalten.
Recht auf Berichtigung gemäß Art. 16 DSGVO
Sie haben das Recht, von uns unverzüglich die Berichtigung Sie betreffender unrichtiger personenbezogener Daten zu verlangen.
Recht auf Löschung gemäß Art. 17 DSGVO
Sie haben das Recht, von uns zu verlangen, dass Sie betreffende personenbezogene Daten unverzüglich gelöscht werden, u.a. dann, wenn die Verarbeitung für den vorgesehenen Zweck nicht mehr notwendig ist oder Sie eine zuvor erteilte Einwilligung widerrrufen und es keine andere gesetzliche Grundlage für die Speicherung gibt.
Recht auf Einschränkung der Verarbeitung gemäß Art. 18 DSGVO
Sie haben das Recht, von uns zu verlangen, die Verarbeitung einzuschränken, insbesondere dann, wenn eine Löschung aus rechtlichen Gründen nicht möglich ist.
Recht auf Datenübertragbarkeit gemäß Art. 20 DSGVO
Sie haben das Recht, die Sie betreffenden personenbezogenen Daten, die Sie uns bereitgestellt haben, in einem strukturierten, gängigen und maschinenlesbaren Format zu erhalten und an Dritte zu übermitteln.
Widerspruchsrecht gemäß Art. 21 DSGVO
Sie haben das Recht, aus Gründen, die sich aus Ihrer besonderen Situation ergeben, jederzeit gegen die Verarbeitung Sie betreffender personenbezogener Daten, die aufgrund von Artikel 6 Absatz 1 Buchstaben e oder f erfolgt, Widerspruch einzulegen; dies gilt auch für ein auf diese Bestimmungen gestütztes Profiling.
Automatisierte Entscheidungen im Einzelfall einschließlich Profiling gemäß Art. 22 DSGVO
Sie haben das Recht, nicht einer ausschließlich auf einer automatisierten Verarbeitung beruhenden Entscheidung unterworfen zu werden, die Ihnen gegenüber rechtliche Wirkung entfaltet oder Sie in ähnlicher Weise erheblich beeinträchtigt.
Widerruf gemäß Art. 7 Abs. 3 DSGVO
Beruht die Verarbeitung Ihrer Daten auf einer Einwilligung, so haben Sie das Recht, Ihre Einwilligung jederzeit zu widerrufen.
Recht auf Beschwerde bei einer Aufsichtsbehörde gemäß Art. 77 DSGVO
Sie haben unbeschadet eines anderweitigen verwaltungsrechtlichen oder gerichtlichen Rechtsbehelfs das Recht auf Beschwerde bei einer Aufsichtsbehörde, insbesondere in dem Mitgliedstaat Ihres gewöhnlichen Aufenthaltsorts, Ihres Arbeitsplatzes oder des Orts des mutmaßlichen Verstoßes.
Imprint -
Privacy Policy -
Terms of Use -
Cookie Consent
Copyright © 2018 TradingDay.com All rights reserved.
All information provided "as is" for informational purposes only, not intended for trading purposes or advice. Neither TradingDay.com nor any of independent providers is liable for any informational errors, incompleteness, or delays, or for any actions taken in reliance on information contained herein.
